The creative director tells us, "
This year I want to work on a world
of butterflies and therefore a
creative vision. We start by building the
yarn, as is all
industrial craftsmanship, then we begin to
weave the yarn and do some tests. The
creative director of Meson then
chooses the ones he likes best from the many tests we give him
. From a
sample we go to production. It's
an industry, there are 200 of us and therefore
we also need an
industrial impact and therefore all
the clothes that go into the shops are made,
so they buy meters and meters and meters of
fabric.
Yes, this is an industry, so then
it seems like everything has only a poetic form
, but in reality many of us earn a
living and it becomes
industrial production. The factory tries to produce the
highest quality and therefore the
highest quality also means producing it in the
most correct time. Time is a cost,
so it becomes a luxury. What
producing slowly also has a meaning which
means I make that fabric in the
most perfect way that in the world
could not be done better. When
I visit the shopping streets of the
most glamorous cities in the world, a lot  stuff
from here.